<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MDA</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>


    <string name="aboutus">
        <br>\n<b>MerDevelop is a blooming IT hub for assisting Digital marketing services, provide staffing and standardized training. Our organization promises enrichment to your brand and empowers you through every challenge. At MerDevelop we metamorphose your obstacles into opportunities and skyrocket you to success.\n</b></br>
        <br>\nOur platform is celebrated for top-notch quality training in the paradigm of Artificial Intelligence, Java, Python, DotNet, Digital Marketing, AWS, and much more. Our robust, resilient and diversified team of experienced professionals offers you expertise training and sharpen you foundational requirements.\n</br>
        <br>\n<b>MerDevelop is specially renowned for our consulting, and digital marketing solutions, through which we strengthens your brand awareness and help you remain one step ahead towards advancements.\n</b></br>
        <br>\nMerDevelop is established with a globally proclaimed mission of catering and garnering consumer’s requirements with ultimate focus and dedication. We express gratefulness to the users who displayed faithfulness in us and warmly welcomes others to join us towards prosperity.\n</br>
        <br>\n<b>We proudly announce that our branches are currently situated in Hyderabad, but we are providing services all across India and US. Our gradually advancing organization is all geared up to answer all your questions, combat all your obstacles and eventually brings forth you ultimate opulence.\n</b></br>


    </string>


    <string name="googleadstraining">

        <br>\nNowadays creative advertisement has taken a major lead in the industry. It has become one of the most popular ways to embrace your audiences’ hearts and oscillate with their evolving emotions.\n</br>
        <br>\nGoogle Ads will definitely benefit you with representing your brand in an incredibly creative way, which will further gain your optimum brand awareness and will improve your brand image.\n</br>
        <br>\nGoogle Ads boost up the lead generation for your brand via creatively addressing your brand to the audiences and furthermore attracting them to invest in your product.\n</br>
        <br>\n1.With Google ads you will be able to influence millions of viewers, embrace your audiences’ hearts and oscillate with their evolving emotions.\n</br>
        <br>\n2.With our Google Ads services, we ensure representing your brand in an incredibly creative way, which will further gain your optimum brand awareness and will improve your brand image.\n</br>
        <br><b>\n3.MerDevelop’s certified digital marketing training solutions will help you understand how to implement the Google Ads trainings in your business and how the system operates with Google Ads. Our diversified team of certified experts explains you about each and every aspect of Google ads and ensure you achieve prosperity in the market.\n</b></br>
  </string>

    <string name="emailmarketing">
        <br>\nEmail marketing is a very effective tool. It helps you to form strong relationships with your consumers and also help you in further communicating with them. Your bond with your customers displays how profitable your business is going to be. Thus, if you wish success for your brand, email marketing is the one-stop solution for it.\n</br>
          <br>\n  With email marketing, you strengthen your brand image that further attracts potential clients towards your business. The technique of email marketing reinforces your brand with a loyal and better brand image that further brings popularity and credibility to your business. \n</br>
        <br>\nEvery single human on earth owns a cell phone in today’s time. It is almost impossible to spot anybody without a cell phone. Email marketing very smartly took advantage of this scenario and has eventually ranked itself one of the best tools to grow popular with this immense craze of mobile phones. With nearly two-thirds of all emails being opened on a mobile device, email marketing is one of the best tools you can use to take advantage of the growing popularity of mobile technology.\n</br>
        <br>\nThus, MerDevelop’s certified digital marketing training course on email marketing enlightens you about various aspects of email marketing and how you can incorporate its advantages in your business. MerDevelop’s digital marketing training solutions brief you about email marketing and its course of actions with their certified team of experts thus, leading you towards success.\n</br>

    </string>

    <string name="payperclicktraining">
        <br>\nPay Per Click or PPC has become an immensely used technique, implemented to increase traffic on your website via paying a certain amount to the publisher, every time your ad is being clicked. \n</br>
        <br>\nPay Per Click Advertising is the paid version of SEO, that will help you with maximizing the website traffic. \n</br>
        <br>\nThe most common example of PPC is Google Ads, which further allows you to pay for the topmost slots on Google’s SERPs. Other mediums for Pay Per Click Advertising include, paid advertisements on Facebook, Twitter advertising campaigns, and sponsored messages on LinkedIn.\n</br>
        <br>\nWith this super easy availability and incredible transparency, Pay Per Click helps you gain a lot of profits and benefits your funds and investments either way. It is because this majority of the marketers are willing to invest in Pay Per Click marketing.\n</br>
        <br>\nHowever, Pay Per Click might get a little complex in the beginning which leads many marketers and investors to commit error. Therefore, MerDevelop’s digital marketing training Pay Per Click marketing services is here to guide you throughout the process. Our experts will ensure about your proper investments and guide you with their experts and wide advises. Enroll for our services now, for we ensure you accomplish success and profits with your brand.\n</br>
    </string>

    <string name="youtubemarketing">
        <br>\nYouTube be marketing comprehends an advanced marketing strategy that generates maximum engagements in your brand campaign via integrating fascinating and impactful videos or advertising your brand via collaborating with popular youtubers. \n</br>
        <br>\nThe 21st century apprehends Videos to be the most versatile and engaging content format the consumers have been observed t enjoy. Videos not only portrays persuasive or dynamic real-life composition but also allows us to allocate it across multiple platforms. \n</br>
        <br>\nYouTube marketing is a brand new terminology that has been introduced in the market. It demands proper understanding of YouTube marketing in order to actually imply it in real life. MerDevelop’s digital marketing training solutions on YouTube marketing perfectly brief you about this particular topic and help you understand about you can achieve success with YouTube marketing in the industry. \n</br>
    </string>

    <string name="webdevelopment">
        <br>\nWeb development trainings help you combat challenges and gear you up for staying ahead in the industrial competition compared to your competitors\n</br>
        <br>\n Web development moreover benefit your organizations with intense productivity and improvement. It allows strict monitoring and control of several aspects of the computing processes that demand operations and enhancement of business productivity.\n</br>
        <br>\nWeb development helps your business to function in less time and with greater accuracy. With web development you can now have all your data integrated into one place, which eventually provides you with greater visibility and real-time information updates.\n</br>
        <br>\nMerDevelop’s web development trainings will offer your business an incredible insight command of programming languages used by experts and will also guide about how they can really be helpful in understanding the industrial trend.\n</br>
        <br>\nMerDevelop’s web development training solutions with certified experts on the team will teach you the necessity of keep your website upgraded and updated with industrial trends. Thus, it is necessary you approach and invest MerDevelop’s web development training solutions for a successful journey in the market.\n</br>
    </string>


    <string name="socialmediamarketing">
        <br>\nIt is indeed commendable how the advancing era of the internet is providing us a broad platform for expressing ourselves in any fashion we want.\n</br>
        <br>\nImplementation of social media marketing summons to be one of our powerful means to conduct business, where we ensure consumers belonging from a different aspect of the industry are served efficiently and judiciously.\n</br>
        <br>\nSocial media marketing helps you construct glorious interactions with various brands and merge a faithful bond with your users. It is a golden opportunity to raise awareness and boost up your brand efficiency and profitability.\n</br>
        <br>\nMarketing your brand throughout the platforms of Facebook, Pinterest and Instagram will bring you remarkable success in the industry.\n</br>


    </string>

    <string name="digitalmarketing">
        <br>\nFrom the onset of Globalization all across the world, Digital marketing has grown rapidly and has brought immense fluidity to the market. Our organization establishes the approaches of Digital marketing for catering to our consumers affluently and integrate our tactic channel of servicing prominently.\n</br>
        <br>\nApplication of Digital marketing in the 21st century harnesses your brand with post-sale and pre-sale leads, develops long-term customer relationships, and enhances your provision of market workflow incredibly in the industry.\n</br>
        <br>\nDigital Marketing is your pathway towards absolute opulence.\n</br>
    </string>


    <string name="seo">
        <br>\nSEO, also summoned as search engine optimization is here to offer your content a powerful boost throughout the entire internet community. Ensuring content quality is indeed crucial but knowing how to advertise it all across the world is a prerequisite.\n</br>
        <br><b>\nOur organization is renowned to add that special touch and glory of SEO to your content and making it shine throughout the globe. Our premium SEO services will help you with optimized delivery of incredible content, that will subsequently maximize incoming traffic to your website and thus, the results will be ever-changing. Leverage your traffic along with profits and leads, and enjoying the ever-escalating sight of skyrocketing business revenue.\n</b></br>
    </string>

    <string name="contentmarketing">
        <br>\nYou must have often heard the phrase, “content is the key”. Your content speaks for your brand. The content you display explains your consumer’s dedication, interest, and faithfulness to your brand.\n</br>
        <br>\nContent marketing is a unique technique performed in marketing that recreates and distributes relevant, valuable, and consistent content for attracting maximum users to your brand and optimize brand awareness.\n</br>
        <br>\nIt true indeed, how over time, the introduction of content has transformed the paradigm of market objectives.\n</br>

    </string>


    <string name="googleadsservices">
       <br>\nEscalate your business like never before, for our Google Ads services will help you accomplish establishing a successful brand image that you have been aiming for from the beginning.\n</br>
       <br>\nNowadays creative advertisement has taken a major lead in the industry. It has become one of the most popular ways to embrace your audiences’ hearts and oscillate with their evolving emotions.\n</br>
       <br>\nGoogle Ads will definitely benefit you with representing your brand in an incredibly creative way, which will further gain your optimum brand awareness and will improve your brand image. \n</br>

   </string>

    <string name="payperclick">
        <br>\nThe Pay Per Click model of the advertisement has become a revolutionary aspect of quantitative measures to enhance your brand performance in the market and optimize your product or service quality.\n</br>
        <br>\nPay Per Click is another unique modulation amidst our digital marketing services that pays you a fixed amount each time a user clicks on your brand advertisement.\n</br>
        <br>\nThis sequence of workflow generates a cost-effective objective and enhances your brand profitability. Apply today and embrace the golden days it brings for your brand.\n</br>
    </string>

    <string name="growbusiness">
        <br>\nMerDevelop is a blooming initiative that vows to be your guiding angle amidst the cutthroat competition in the industry. Merge with us and let us assist you with our renowned, affluent, and readily available digital marketing services. We assure you complete transparency while servicing and ensure ultimate opulence and top-notch outcome.\n</br>
        <br>\nJoin us now!</br>

    </string>
</resources>